<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><cheatsheet title="Kobold Tutorial">	<intro 		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf">		<description>			Welcome to the Kobold tutorial.			The primary purpose of Kobold is to provide a tool for the development			and maintenance of software product lines. Kobold also supports the			establishment of a role-based development process.			This tutorial will introduce you to the user interface and to be able to 			work with Kobold right away.			Let's get started!		</description>	</intro>	<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf"		title="Open the Kobold Perspective">		<description>			Select Window-&gt;Open Perspective-&gt;Other...-&gt;Kobold Productline in the menubar at			the top of the workbench. This step changes the perspective to			set up the Eclipse workbench for Kobold. 		</description>	</item>	<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf"		title="Set the Kobold Client properties">		<description>			When you use the Kobold Client Feature Set for the first time, you will need			to set its properties. Select Window-&gt;Preferences-&gt;Kobold			and fill in the textfields. If necessary, look up the exact steps in the Kobold			tutorial.		</description>	</item>	<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf"		title="Create a Kobold project">		<description>			In order to work with Kobold you will need a Kobold Project. 			Select File-&gt;New-&gt;Project...			and choose Kobold PLAM Project in the list. Complete the subsequent			pages as required. If necessary, look up the exact steps in the Kobold			tutorial.		</description>	</item>	<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf" 		title="The Role Tree">		<description>			The Role Tree on the left side shows your created Kobold project. When you open it, 			it displays the name of the productline, its architecture, its core assets and its products.			By double-clicking on the Architecture sign you complete this step.		</description>	</item>	<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf"		title="The Architecture">		<description>			The Architecture View opens in the center of the window. Here you can create and view			your architecture. If you right-click on an item and select "configure", you can change the			meta information of the item. The palette on the right sight provides tools to create your			architecture.		</description>	</item>		<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf"		title="Create your own architecture">		<description>			By clicking on the palette it opens and you can use the tools. First of all, select "component"			and create two new components in your architecture through drag and drop. You can connect			the two components by selecting the "include" or "exclude edge" and clicking on each of the			components. The same way you created components, you can place variants inside components			and releases inside variants. In order to find out more, look up the "node-related" chapter in the			Kobold tutorial.		</description>	</item>		<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf"		title="The Outline">		<description>			In the bottom left of your window you can see the Outline. It displays a miniature of the architecture 			you just created. If the architecture is bigger than the Architecture View can display at the same time, 			you can navigate through the architecture by clicking on the spot in the Outline you want to center.		</description>	</item>		<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf"		title="The Workflow View">		<description>			Kobold offers another view: The Workflow View. It displays the messages the current user got when 			the project is selected. If you want to check for new messages, simply open the menu in the Workflow			View and select "Fetch Messages". The Workflow View also offers you the possibility to send a mail			and, if you are a programmer, to suggest a file for a core group.		</description>	</item>		<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf"		title="Send a message">		<description>			Let's send ourselves a new mail! Open the menu of the Workflow View and select "new mail". A dialog			opens where you can enter the recipient, subject and message of your mail. Press the "send" button and			check your mails right away as described in the last step. 		</description>	</item>	<item		href="/kobold.client.plam/CheatSheets/usermanual.pdf"		title="Still more questions...">		<description>			If you find that there are still some open questions on your mind, simply open the Kobold tutorial			to find out more about Kobold. Thank you!		</description>	</item></cheatsheet>